Finding Aid for Men's Glee Club (University of Michigan) records 1886-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sound Recordings
  - Reel-to-Reel Tapes
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & University of Illinois Glee Club Combine Concert, 1964 November 07; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-30-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; University of Illinois performs: Praise Ye The Lord; Hymne; Steersman, Leave the Watch!; Oh What Delight; Arriero, Canta!; The Boatmen's Dance; Voyagers; Big Ten Medley. The Michigan Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; O Magnum Mysterium; Tobacco; Glory to God in the Highest. Selections by the Arbors: Let Beauty Awake; The Infinite Shining Heaven; She's Like a Swallow; A Taste of Honey; Little Brown Jug; Garota de Ipanema; Luck, Be a Lady; Michigan Songs; Presentation to Alumni of Outstanding Achievement Awards by President Harlan Hatcher. Both Glee Clubs perform their University's Alma Maters: Hail to the Orange; The Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-30-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; University of Illinois performs: Praise Ye The Lord; Hymne; Steersman, Leave the Watch!; Oh What Delight; Arriero, Canta!; The Boatmen's Dance; Voyagers; Big Ten Medley. The Michigan Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; O Magnum Mysterium; Tobacco; Glory to God in the Highest. Selections by the Arbors: Let Beauty Awake; The Infinite Shining Heaven; She's Like a Swallow; A Taste of Honey; Little Brown Jug; Garota de Ipanema; Luck, Be a Lady; Michigan Songs; Presentation to Alumni of Outstanding Achievement Awards by President Harlan Hatcher. Both Glee Clubs perform their University's Alma Maters: Hail to the Orange; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 106th Annual Spring Concert, 1965 March 27; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-31-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Michigan Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; O Magnum Mysterium; El Grillo; The Lord is a Man of War; Alleluia; My Lovely Celia; Song of the Flea; When I was a Lad; Alleluia; Frostiana; In That New Jerusalem; Garota de Ipanema; Great Day; Old King Cole; A Taste of Honey; It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World; I'm Always Chasing Rainbows; What Kind of Fool Am I; Accentuate the Positive; He Walked Right In; Tonight; You Make Me Feel So Young; Ridin' High; It's a Big, Wide, Wonderful World; Climb Every Mountain; The Friars perform a selection of Michigan Songs.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-31-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Michigan Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; O Magnum Mysterium; El Grillo; The Lord is a Man of War; Alleluia; My Lovely Celia; Song of the Flea; When I was a Lad; Alleluia; Frostiana; In That New Jerusalem; Garota de Ipanema;Great Day; Old King Cole; A Taste of Honey; It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World; I'm Always Chasing Rainbows; What Kind of Fool Am I; Accentuate the Positive; He Walked Right In; Tonight; You Make Me Feel So Young; Ridin' High; It's a Big, Wide, Wonderful World; Climb Every Mountain; The Friars perform a selection of Michigan Songs.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & Kwansei Gakuin Glee Club, 1965 October 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-32-1-1]; mp3 file; (American and Japanese National Anthems; Missa Tempore Belli; Kyrie; Gloria; Sanctus; Benedictus; Agnus Dei; Series of the Yanagawa River: The Yanagawa River; Dyer's Daughter; Iris; A Lull in the Rainy Season; Aino Race's Melody Whale Festival; Bear Festival; Children's Song; Prayer in Solar/ Lunar Eclipse; Love Song; Dance Song; Seeing Nellie Home; Love's Old Sweet Song; Li'l Liza Jane; Aura Lee; Good Night Ladies; Soranbushi Fisherman Song; Konpira Funefune Samisen Melody; Mogamigawa Boatman Song; Shrine Festival Eve; Buddha's Festival; Yagibushi Farmer's Festival.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & New York University Glee Club Combined Concert, 1965 October 30; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-33-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The New York University Glee Club performs: Mater Patris et Filia; Gloria; Hospodi Pomiloi; El Yivneh Hagalili; (Goliards) Collegiate Composite. The Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Confitemini Domino; El Grillo; Good Fellows, Be Merry; The Celestial Vision Part II; Frostiana; Garota de Ipanema; In that New Jerusalem; The Begat; It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World; I'm Always Chasing Rainbows; What Kind of Fool Am I; Accentuate the Positive; He Walked Right In; Tonight; You Make Me Feel So Young; Ridin' High; It's a Big, Wide, Wonderful World; Climb Every Mountain; Michigan Songs. The combined Glee Clubs perform their University's Alma Maters: The Palisades; The Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-33-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The New York University Glee Club performs: Mater Patris et Filia; Gloria; Hospodi Pomiloi; El Yivneh Hagalili; (Goliards) Collegiate Composite. The Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Confitemini Domino; El Grillo; Good Fellows, Be Merry; The Celestial Vision Part II; Frostiana; Garota de Ipanema; In that New Jerusalem; The Begat; It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World; I'm Always Chasing Rainbows; What Kind of Fool Am I; Accentuate the Positive; He Walked Right In; Tonight; You Make Me Feel So Young; Ridin' High; It's a Big, Wide, Wonderful World; Climb Every Mountain; Michigan Songs. The combined Glee Clubs perform their University's Alma Maters: The Palisades; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 107th Annual Spring Concert, 1966 April 02; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-34-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Confitemini Domino; Come My Beloved; Hymn To The Eternal; Night and Dreams; Good Fellows Be Merry; La Virgen de la Macarena; The Bugler's Holiday; Saints; A Song of Joy; The Heart Worships; Shadrack; Blow, Gabriel, Blow; It's A Grand Night for Singing; If There is Someone Lovelier Than You; Who; All the Things You Are; I Know that You Know; Good Night Sweetheart; Some Enchanted Evening; I Got Rhythm; Friars (selections; Michigan Songs; Encores by the Friars.))
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-34-2-1]; mp3 file; (The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Confitemini Domino; Come My Beloved; Hymn To The Eternal; Night and Dreams; Good Fellows Be Merry; La Virgen de la Macarena; The Bugler's Holiday; Saints; A Song of Joy; The Heart Worships; Shadrack; Blow, Gabriel, Blow; It's A Grand Night for Singing; If There is Someone Lovelier Than You; Who; All the Things You Are; I Know that You Know; Good Night Sweetheart; Some Enchanted Evening; I Got Rhythm; Friars (selections; Michigan Songs; Encores by the Friars.))
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club Pressing Master, 1966 June 21; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-35-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Confitemini Domino; Come My Beloved; Hymn To The Eternal; Good Fellows Be Merry; A Song of Joy; The Heart Worships; Shadrack; Blow, Gabriel, Blow; In That New Jerusalem; Pentagonitis.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-35-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Confitemini Domino; Come My Beloved; Hymn To The Eternal; Good Fellows Be Merry; A Song of Joy; The Heart Worships; Shadrack; Blow, Gabriel, Blow; In That New Jerusalem; Pentagonitis.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 3rd Annual Bandorama, 1966 October 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-36-1-1]; mp3 file; (The Friars perform selections ad Libitum; The Marching Band The Marching Band w/announcer, William D. Revelli, conductor, George Cavender, assistant conductor performing "M" Fanfare; The Men up Front, David Smith, drum major, Richard Follett, Mike Jones, twirlers, March Garland Entree; Buglers Holiday; Old Man River from Showboat; On The Trail from the Grand Canyon Suite; Muskrat Ramble; Spanish Flea; Sing, Sing, Sing; Temptation; Hawaiian War Chant; Campus Memories; I Want to Go Back to Michigan; Bum Army. The Men's Glee Club: Laudes Atqua Carmina; Varsity; College Days; The Victors; America.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & Northwestern University Glee Club Joint Concert, 1966 November 12; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-37-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Northwestern University Glee Club performs: Now Let Every Tongue Adore Thee; Art Thou With Me; Zion Hears The Watchmen Singing; Habanera; The Testament of Freedom, I. The God Who Gave Us Life, III. We Fight No For Glory, IV. I Shall No Die Without Hope; Those Broadway Gals: Mame; - Jerry Herman, Gigi (Gigi), Frederick Loewe, Dolly (Hello, Dolly); The University of MichiganPresentation to Alumni of outstanding achievement awards by President Harlan Hatcher (9:30 p.m. concert). The Michigan Men's Glee Club; Laudes Atque carmina; Dona Nobis Pacem; Chorus of the Returning Pilgrims; Lord Randall; My Good Ol' Man; Stomp Your Foot; The Bugler's Holiday; It's a Grand Night for Singing; If There is Someone Lovelier Than You; Who; All the Things You Are; I Know That You Know; Good Night Sweetheart; Some Enchanted Evening; I Got Rhythm. Selections of Michigan songs by The Friars. Combined Glee Clubs perform Alma Maters - Hail Northwestern; The Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-37-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Northwestern University Glee Club performs: Now Let Every Tongue Adore Thee; Art Thou With Me; Zion Hears The Watchmen Singing; Habanera; The Testament of Freedom, I. The God Who Gave Us Life, III. We Fight No For Glory, IV. I Shall No Die Without Hope; Those Broadway Gals: Mame; - Jerry Herman, Gigi (Gigi), Frederick Loewe, Dolly (Hello, Dolly); The University of MichiganPresentation to Alumni of outstanding achievement awards by President Harlan Hatcher (9:30 p.m. concert). The Michigan Men's Glee Club; Laudes Atque carmina; Dona Nobis Pacem; Chorus of the Returning Pilgrims; Lord Randall; My Good Ol' Man; Stomp Your Foot; The Bugler's Holiday; It's a Grand Night for Singing; If There is Someone Lovelier Than You; Who; All the Things You Are; I Know That You Know; Good Night Sweetheart; Some Enchanted Evening; I Got Rhythm. Selections of Michigan songs by The Friars. Combined Glee Clubs perform Alma Maters - Hail Northwestern; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club "Michigan Songs", 1967 March 09; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [87250-SR-38-1-1]; mp3 file; (Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Michigan Medley; Goddess of the Inland Seas; Go Blue; Michigan Men; I'll Never Forget My College Days; Drink, Drink, Joy Rules the Day; The University; Hymn to Michigan; Bum Army; Old Friars Song; When Night Falls; Ann Arbor Days; Varsity; Victors; Yellow and Blue)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 108th Annual Spring Concert, 1967 April 01; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-39-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Dona Nobis Pacem; Ave Verum Corpus; Echo Song; Heigh Ho! For a Husband; Hallelujah, Amen; Concert Etude, Number 3, D flat Major; Ravido ed Ostinato; Encore, Argentine Dance #2; The Ravens of Owein; I Hear an Army; Go, Lovely Rose; The Pirate Song; Who Shall Speak For the People; Balm in Gilead; Trumpeters Holiday; Pollution.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-39-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Selections performed include: Speak to Me of Love; What is this Thing Called Love?; Love is the Sweetest Thing; Love is a Many Splendored Thing; Love is a Simple Thing; Would You Like to Take a Walk?; Strange Music; I Met a Girl; Soft Lights and Sweet Music; 'S Wonderful 'S Marvelous; Our Love is Here to Stay; Love is Sweeping the Country; Selections by The Friars: If I could Write a Symphony, Mr. Bass Man, Encore, I am Only Eighteen; Michigan Songs: Michigan Medley, Michigan Men; Goddess of the Inland Seas; Bum Army; Go Blue; Old Friars Song; Varsity and Victors; The Yellow and Blue. )
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 108th Annual Spring Concert Pressing Master, 1967 June 11; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-40-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Songs performed include: Laudes Atque Carmina; Ave Verum Corpus; Echo Song; Hallelujah, Amen; Ravido ed Ostinato; The Pirate Song; Who Shall Speak For the People; Balm in Gilead; Stomp Your Foot.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-40-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Songs performed are: Pollution; Speak to Me of Love; Symphony for Susan; Go Blue!; Old Friars Song; Varsity, Victors; Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & Ohio State University Glee Club Join Concert, 1967 November 04; 2Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-41-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Ohio State University Glee Club performs: Father William; Arise O Ye Servants of God; Mgdlein in Walde; Stars of the Summer Night. The Impromptus perform selections: Rock A My Soul; Johnny Stiles; When Johnny Comes Marching Home; Campus Echoes. The Michigan Glee Club performs Laudes Atque Carmina; Dona Nobis Pacem; Ave Verum Corpus; The Omnipotence. Bob Mac Grath performs: The Vagabond; Money, O!; Who Shall Speak For the People; The Arbors (selections); Michigan Songs; (The Alma Maters) Carmen Ohio; The Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-41-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Ohio State University Glee Club performs: Father William; Arise O Ye Servants of God; Mgdlein in Walde; Stars of the Summer Night. The Impromptus perform selections: Rock A My Soul; Johnny Stiles; When Johnny Comes Marching Home; Campus Echoes. The Michigan Glee Club performs Laudes Atque Carmina; Dona Nobis Pacem; Ave Verum Corpus; The Omnipotence. Bob Mac Grath performs: The Vagabond; Money, O!; Who Shall Speak For the People; The Arbors (selections); Michigan Songs; (The Alma Maters) Carmen Ohio; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 109th Annual Spring Concert, 1968 March 23; 2Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-42-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Invocation of Orpheus; Dona Nobis Pacem; Confitemini Domino; The Omnipotence; Waltz in A Flat Op 12, Chopin; Golliwog's Cakewalk; Songs of Travel; Money, O; She's Like a Swallow; Truth Shall Deliver; Luck Be A Lady; Sons of Jimmy Brown; Handwhistler; Pollution.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-42-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Michigan Men's Glee Club performs: And the Night Shall Be Filled With Music; Stardust; Dream; Deep Purple; Laura; Did You Ever See a Dream Walking; In the Still of the Night; The Most Beautiful Girl in the World. Michigan Songs by the Friars.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club 109th Annual Spring Concert Pressing Master, 1968 March 23; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-43-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Confitemini Domino; The Omnipotence; Waltz in A Flat Opus 12; Songs of Travel Pt 2; Money, O; Truth Shall Deliver; Luck be a Lady; Pollution.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-43-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: And the Night Shall be Filled with Music; Klu Klux Klan; Michigan Medley; Michigan Men; Go Blue!; Drink! Drink!; Varsity and The Victors; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & University of Illinois Varsity Glee Club Join Concert, 1968 November 09; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-44-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Illinois Glee Club performs: Marching Song of the Illini; Gaudeamus Igitur; Cantate Domino; The God Who Gave Us Life; I Shall Not Die Without a Hope; Here's To The Maiden; Sometimes I Feel Like a Motherless Child; Set Down Servant; People; You'll Never Walk Alone; Big Ten Medley; Marching Song of the Illini. The Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; A Mighty Fortress; O Magnum Mysterium; Then Round About the Starry Throne; Il Balen del Suo Sorisso; Soliloquy; It Ain't Necessarily So; Is My Team Plowing; Truth Shall Deliver; Old King Cole; Friars (selections); Michigan Songs; (Alma Maters) Hail To The Orange; Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-44-2-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Illinois Glee Club performs: Marching Song of the Illini; Gaudeamus Igitur; Cantate Domino; The God Who Gave Us Life; I Shall Not Die Without a Hope; Here's To The Maiden; Sometimes I Feel Like a Motherless Child; Set Down Servant; People; You'll Never Walk Alone; Big Ten Medley; Marching Song of the Illini. The Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; A Mighty Fortress; O Magnum Mysterium; Then Round About the Starry Throne; Il Balen del Suo Sorisso; Soliloquy; It Ain't Necessarily So; Is My Team Plowing; Truth Shall Deliver; Old King Cole; Friars (selections); Michigan Songs; (Alma Maters) Hail To The Orange; Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-44-2-1-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Illinois Glee Club performs: Marching Song of the Illini; Gaudeamus Igitur; Cantate Domino; The God Who Gave Us Life; I Shall Not Die Without a Hope; Here's To The Maiden; Sometimes I Feel Like a Motherless Child; Set Down Servant; People; You'll Never Walk Alone; Big Ten Medley; Marching Song of the Illini. The Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; A Mighty Fortress; O Magnum Mysterium; Then Round About the Starry Throne; Il Balen del Suo Sorisso; Soliloquy; It Ain't Necessarily So; Is My Team Plowing; Truth Shall Deliver; Old King Cole; Friars (selections); Michigan Songs; (Alma Maters) Hail To The Orange; Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club "White Tie and Tails", 1969 March 29; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-45-1-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Michigan Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; A Mighty Fortress; O Magnum Mysterium; Ave Maria; The Lord is a Man of War; Alleluia; Beautiful Blue Danube; Beethoven's Appassionata with It's Alright With Me; Alleluia; The Celestial Vision; Is My Team Plowing?; A Taste of Honey; County Fair.)
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-45-1-1-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Michigan Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; A Mighty Fortress; O Magnum Mysterium; Ave Maria; The Lord is a Man of War; Alleluia; Beautiful Blue Danube; Beethoven's Appassionata with It's Alright With Me; Alleluia; The Celestial Vision; Is My Team Plowing?; A Taste of Honey; County Fair.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-45-2-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: The Echo Song; Ain't Got the Time To Die; Old Rocking Chair's Got Me; Of Thee I Sing; I Get a Kick Out of You; Hey There; They Didn't Believe Me; All the Things You Are; And This is My Beloved; You're The Top; Thank Heaven for Little Girls; The Friars (selections); (Michigan Songs) Tis of Michigan We Sing; A Toast to Michigan; I Want To Go Back To Michigan; Michigan Men; Goddess of the Inland Seas; Go Blue; The Friars' Drinking Song; The Bum Army; The Old Friars' Song; Varsity; Victors; I'll Never Forget My College Days; Yellow and Blue.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1-2], [87250-SR-45-2-1-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; The Men's Glee Club performs: The Echo Song; Ain't Got the Time To Die; Old Rocking Chair's Got Me; Of Thee I Sing; I Get a Kick Out of You; Hey There; They Didn't Believe Me; All the Things You Are; And This is My Beloved; You're The Top; Thank Heaven for Little Girls; The Friars (selections); (Michigan Songs) Tis of Michigan We Sing; A Toast to Michigan; I Want To Go Back To Michigan; Michigan Men; Goddess of the Inland Seas; Go Blue; The Friars' Drinking Song; The Bum Army; The Old Friars' Song; Varsity; Victors; I'll Never Forget My College Days; Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club Pressing Master, 1969 June 22; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-46-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; Side 1; The Men's Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; The Lord is a Man of War; The Celestial Vision; A Taste of Honey; Echo Song; Ain't Got Time To Die; Old Rockin' Chair.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1], [87250-SR-46-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Side 2; Alleluia; Dizzy; Appassionata and It's All Right; Go Blue; Bum Army; Varsity and Victors; Dr. Philip A Duey; The Yellow and Blue.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club & Ohio State University Men's Glee Club Joint Concert, 1969 November 22; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Tape 1, Part 1], [87250-SR-47-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1 of 2; The Ohio State Glee Club performs: I Will Sing Unto The Lord; Et in Terra Pax; The Agincourt Song; Come, Ye Thankful People, Come; Old Mother Hubbard; Georgie Girl, piano Impromptu; Halls of Ivy; Once Upon a Happy Time; Gonna Build a Mountain; Campus Echoes.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-47-2-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Emitte Spiritum; Kyrie at Sea; A Mighty Fortress Is Our God; As Beautiful As She; The Lord is My Light. Selections by the Friars: Impatience; If Ever I Would Leave You; Blowin' In The Wind; Mac Arthur Park; Elijah Rock; Balm in Gilead; Good News; Michigan Songs; The Combined Glee Clubs perform their University Alma Maters: Carmen Ohio; The Yellow and Blue. Presentation to alumni of Outstanding Achievement Awards by President Robben W. Fleming.)
      - [Tape 2, Part 1-2, [87250-SR-47-2-1-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Emitte Spiritum; Kyrie at Sea; A Mighty Fortress Is Our God; As Beautiful As She; The Lord is My Light. Selections by the Friars: Impatience; If Ever I Would Leave You; Blowin' In The Wind; Mac Arthur Park; Elijah Rock; Balm in Gilead; Good News; Michigan Songs; The Combined Glee Clubs perform their University Alma Maters: Carmen Ohio; The Yellow and Blue. Presentation to alumni of Outstanding Achievement Awards by President Robben W. Fleming.)
    - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club Annual Spring Concert, 1970 April 3; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch
      - [Tape 1, Part 1-1], [87250-SR-48-1-1-1]; mp3 file; (The Michigan Glee Club performs: Laudes Atque Carmina; Dona Nobis Pacem; Emmitte Spiritum; The Lord is My Light; Chorus of the Returning Pilgrims; Impatience; As Beautiful As She; I Love My Love; Five Nature Studies - The Urge; The Scripts Are Ready; A True Portend; Time To Sleep; The Discovery; If Ever I Would Leave You; Elijah; Were You There; Good News; Everytime I Feel The Spirit; Pollution; Wichita Lineman; MacArthur Park; What the World Needs Now; 'Tis of Michigan We Sing; A Toast to Michigan; I Wanna Go Back to Michigan; Drink, Drink, Joy Rules the Day; The Bum Army; Goddess of the Inland Seas; Michigan Men; The Old Friars' Song; Varsity and the Victors; Yellow and The Blue.)